School of Communication fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Curriculum files, 1975 - 1992; F-92-5; 1.37 m of textual records
  Some records contain personal information relating to students or faculty. Access to these files is restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
  - Curriculum development files, 1975 - 1988; F-92-5-1; 31 cm of textual records
    - Courses: curriculum rationalization, 1986 - 1987; F-92-5-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Courses: program planning, 1985 - 1986; F-92-5-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - New course proposals, 1983 - 1984; F-92-5-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Course proposals - new courses, 1986 - 1988; F-92-5-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Course proposals - existing courses (up to 1988-3), 1980 - 1988; F-92-5-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Grades: general, 1980 - 1985; F-92-5-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Undergraduate grading, 1985 - 1988; F-92-5-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Grades: Ombudsoffice, 1984; F-92-5-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 92-9)
    - Courses: evaluations, surveys, 1985 - 1986; F-92-5-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Courses: breadth requirements and prerequisites, 1985 - 1987; F-92-5-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Stats: credit-free instruction, 1982 - 1987; F-92-5-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Courses: cross listings, 1987; F-92-5-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Canadian Studies, 1977 - 1983; F-92-5-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Courses: Sociology / Anthropology conflict, 1986 - 1987; F-92-5-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Courses: Arts Management Program, 1986 - 1987; F-92-5-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Maths / Stats course proposal, 1986; F-92-5-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Guest lecturers / visitors: general, vol. 1, 1976 - 1984; F-92-5-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Guest lecturers / visitors: general, vol. 2, 1976 - 1984; F-92-5-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Guest lecturers / visitors: general, vol. 3, 1976 - 1984; F-92-5-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 92-10)
    - Programs of Distinction, 1979 - 1982; F-92-5-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Continuing Studies - SFU downtown, 1979 - 1981; F-92-5-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Continuing Studies, 1975 - 1983; F-92-5-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Courses: proposed Commonwealth University, 1987; F-92-5-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Departmental conferences, 1984 - 1987; F-92-5-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Ph.D. (CMNS) proposal, 1982 - 1983; F-92-5-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Proposal for Ph.D. program in communications at SFU, 1982; F-92-5-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
    - Appendix 14 - Ph.D. program proposal, 1982; F-92-5-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
  - Course files, 1976 - 1992; F-92-5-2; 1.06 m of textual records
    - General file, 1976; F-92-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1978 - 1979; F-92-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1980; F-92-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1981; F-92-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1982; F-92-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1983; F-92-5-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1984; F-92-5-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1985; F-92-5-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1987; F-92-5-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1988; F-92-5-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1989; F-92-5-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1990; F-92-5-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - General file, 1991; F-92-5-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - CMNS 100-3 Explorations in Communications, 1976 - 1978; F-92-5-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - CMNS 110-3 Introduction to Communication Theory, 1985 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - CMNS 110-3 Introduction to Communication Theory (evening), 1988 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - CMNS 120-3 Explorations in Interpersonal Communication, 1978 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 92-12)
    - CMNS 130-3 Explorations in Mass Communication, 1978 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 130-3 Explorations in Mass Communication, 1984 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 130-3 Explorations in Mass Communication, 1989 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 130-3 Explorations in Mass Communication (evening), 1987 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 200-3 The Pragmatics of Communication / Introduction to Communication Theory, 1979 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 201-3 Introduction to Human Communication Networks, 1988 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 210-3 History of Communication, 1984 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 215-3 Advertising as Social Communication, 1982 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 215-3 Advertising as Social Communication, 1984 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 92-13)
    - CMNS 215-3 Advertising as Social Communication, 1980 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 215-3 Advertising as Social Communication (evening), 1985 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 220-3 Understanding Television / Introduction to Interpersonal Communication, 1979 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 221-3 Media and Audiences, 1987 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 222-3 Communication in Cultural Context, 1979; F-92-5-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 224-3 Communication and Creativity, 1983; F-92-5-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 225-3 Introduction to Interpersonal Communication, 1988 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 230-3 Introduction to Communication Media, 1979 - 1982; F-92-5-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
      Access review (Sep 8, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (1) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 230-3 Introduction to Communication Media, 1983 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 230-3 Introduction to Communication Media, 1988 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 232-3 Urban Communication Networks, 1979; F-92-5-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 240-3 The Political Economy of Communication, 1980 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
      Access review (Sep 8, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (5) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 250-3 Introduction to Empirical Methods for Communication Research, 1992; F-92-5-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 253-3 Computers and Communication / Intro to Information Technology: The New Media, 1980 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
      Access review (Sep 7, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (5) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 257-3 Explorations in Video, 1979 - 1982; F-92-5-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 92-14)
    - CMNS 258-3 Introduction to Electroacoustic Communication, 1979 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 258-3 Introduction to Electroacoustic Communication, 1984 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 259-3 Acoustic Dimensions of Communication, 1979 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 261-3 Documentary Research in Communication, 1990 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 300-5 Introduction to Systems Theory, 1979 - 1981; F-92-5-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 301-4 Communication Network Research Methods, 1988 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 302-4 Communication Network Research, 1989 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 303-3 Communication as a Biosocial Process, 1980 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 304-4 Communication and The Language of Everyday Life, 1979 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 310-4 History of Communication Thought / Communication Thought in the Evolution of the Social Sciences, 1979 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 315-4 Cultural Dimensions in Advertising, 1987 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 320-5 Communication Processes and Interpersonal Behaviour I, 1979 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 321-4 Communication and Culture in Musical Form / The Popular Idiom / The Cultural Production of Popular Music, 1982 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 322-3 Communication in Conflict and Intervention, 1980 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 323-3 Communication Processes and Individual Behaviour, 1979 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 324-3 Communication and Creativity, 1979 - 1981; F-92-5-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 92-15)
    - CMNS 325-4 Interpersonal Communication and the Mass Media, 1988 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 330-5 Communication and Cultural Form, 1979 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 331-5 Communications Media: Theory and Research I, 1979 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 333-4 Communication Policy in Canada / Broadcast Regulation and Policy in Canada, 1979 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 334-4 Cultural Policy, 1988 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 335-4 The Newspaper Industry and Press Policy in Canada, 1988 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 336-3 Social Changes and Community Media, 1979; F-92-5-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 340-3 The Political Economy of the Radio Spectrum and Telecommunications, 1980; F-92-5-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 341-4 Political Communication, 1983 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
      Access review (Sep 7, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (4) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history, educational history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 342-4 Science and Public Policy I: Risk Communication, 1988 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 346-4 International Communication, 1988 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 353-4 The Social Impact of Information Technology, 1985 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 357-3 Video Techniques and Applications, 1979 - 1981; F-92-5-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 358-3 Sound Tape Recording: Theory and Uses, 1979 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 359-3 Acoustic Dimensions of Communication II, 1979 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 360-4 Fundamentals of Communication Research, 1979 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 92-16)
    - CMNS 361-4 Documentary Research in Communication, 1979 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-74 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 362-4 Field Methods in Communication Research / Evaluation Methods in Applied Communication Research, 1979 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-75 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 371-4 The Structure of the Book Publishing Industry in Canada, 1987 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-76 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 372-4 The Publishing Process, 1989 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-77 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 400-5 Communication Theory; Systemic Formulations / Context Theory, 1979 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-78 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 402-5 Communication in Organizations: A System Approach, 1979 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-79 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 404-5 The Ecology of Communication, 1979 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-80 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
      Access review (Sep 7, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (2) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 410-5 Communication Thought in the Evolution of the Social Sciences II, 1981 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-81 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
      Access review (Sep 6, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (2) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 420-5 Communication processes and Interpersonal Behaviour II, 1979 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-82 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 421-4 Issues Seminar, 1987 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-83 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 422-4 Media and Ideology, 1988 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-84 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 425-5 Seminar in Communication Processes, 1983 - 1985; F-92-5-2-0-85 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 430-4 Communications and Cultural Form II, 1979; F-92-5-2-0-86 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 431-5 Communication Media: Theory and Research II, 1981 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-87 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 433-5 Issues in Communication Policy, 1979 - 1990; F-92-5-2-0-88 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
      Access review (Sep 6, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (6) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history, educational history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 436-4 Communication and Rural Development, 1983 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-89 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
      Access review (Sep 6, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (3) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 437-5 Media, Education and Children / Communication and Community Advocacy, 1979 - 1981; F-92-5-2-0-90 (Archival box - standard 92-17)
    - CMNS 439-4 Media Production and Analysis / Field Practice, 1984 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-91 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 442-4 Science and Public Policy II: Standards, 1990; F-92-5-2-0-92 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 444-5 The Political Economy of International Communications, 1979 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-93 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
      Access review (Aug 24, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (4) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 445-5 Canadian Institutions in International Development: The Hidden Context of Communication, 1979 - 1982; F-92-5-2-0-94 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
      Access review (Aug 24, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (1) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 446-4 The Communication of Science and the Transfer of Technology, 1988 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-95 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 448-5 Telecommunication Regulation in North America, 1981 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-96 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
      Access review (Aug 24, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (3) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 453-5 The Information Society, 1984 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-97 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 470-5 Book Publishing in Canada, 1980 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-98 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 471-4 Selected Topics in Publishing, 1988 - 1991; F-92-5-2-0-99 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 480-2 Directed Study, 1979 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-100 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 480-2 Directed Study, 1988 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-101 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 481-3 Directed Study, 1979 - 1983; F-92-5-2-0-102 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 481-3 Directed Study, 1984 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-103 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 482-4 Directed Study, 1979 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-104 (Archival box - standard 92-18)
    - CMNS 482-4 Directed Study, 1990 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-105 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 483-5 Directed Study, 1979 - 1982; F-92-5-2-0-106 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 483-5 Directed Study, 1983 - 1987; F-92-5-2-0-107 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 486-3 Special Topics in Communication, 1979 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-108 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 487-5 Special Topics in Communication, 1979 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-109 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 498-18 Individual Study Seminar, 1979 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-110 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 499-15 Individual Study Seminar, 1981 - 1992; F-92-5-2-0-111 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 800-5 Contemporary Approaches in Communication Studies, 1979 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-112 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
      Access review (Aug 24, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - CMNS 801-5 Design and Methodology in Communication Research, 1979 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-113 (Archival box - standard 92-19)
    - CMNS 802-5 History of Communication Theory, 1979 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-114 (Archival box - small 92-20)
      Access review (Aug 23, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - CMNS 805-5 Communication Research Methods and Techniques, 1985 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-115 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 810-5 Advanced Communication Theory, 1989; F-92-5-2-0-116 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 815-5 The Social Matrix of Communication, 1985 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-117 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 820-5 Interpersonal and Group Processes, 1980 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-118 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 825-5 The Social Matrix of Communication, 1982 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-119 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 830-5 Communication Media: Research and Development, 1984 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-120 (Archival box - small 92-20)
      Access review (Aug 23, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (1) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (educational history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - CMNS 834-5 The Political Economy of Communications, 1978 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-121 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 839-5 Acoustic Dimensions of Communication, 1980 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-122 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 840-5 Critical Theory of Communication / Advanced Communication Theory, 1980 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-123 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 845-5 Communication and International Development, 1985 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-124 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 850-5 General Graduate Studies, 1986 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-125 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 855-5 Selected Topics, 1981 - 1984; F-92-5-2-0-126 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 856-5 Graduate Seminar, 1981 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-127 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 859-5 Acoustic Dimensions of Communication, 1986 - 1988; F-92-5-2-0-128 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 860-2 Graduate Colloquium, 1981 - 1989; F-92-5-2-0-129 (Archival box - small 92-20)
    - CMNS 885-2 Ph.D. Colloquium, 1984; F-92-5-2-0-130 (Archival box - small 92-20)
- Publications, 1986 - 1996; F-92-6; 3 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications created by the School and its predecessors. Material includes "CMNS news," the departmental newsletter; annual reports; and course outline booklets.
  For detailed records on courses described in the Course outline booklets, see "Course files" (sub-series F-92-5-2).
  The files are open with no restrictions.
  - CMNS News [departmental newsletter], 1995 - 1996; F-92-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
  - School of Communication Annual Report, 1993 - 1994; F-92-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 92-11)
  - Course outline booklets, 1986 - 1988; F-92-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 92-11)